

Burak Tamince

Date of birth: 10/07/2002

Nationality: Turkish

Gender: Male

CONTACT

34930 Istanbul, Türkiye (Home)

btamince@gmail.com

https://github.com/Athena65 (Gith ub)

https://instagram.com/tmncburak

https://stackoverflow.com/users/ 19648244/burak-tamince (StackO verflow)

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/ burak-tamince/

ABOUT ME

I have been studying in Gedik University as a computer Engineer. I graduated from Kartal Anatolian Highschool. I'm into computer programing, object oriented programming, artifical intelligence development. When i do my job i do with my %100 potential, I do my best .Also in C and C# language a have 2 years of experience. I can make all my search using Translate extension in English documentation easily.

WORK EXPERIENCE

12/02/2024 - CURRENT İstanbul, Türkiye

Programmer Waytogo Digital Coaching Platform

- Making Back-End, Front-End, Database operations via PHP, MySQL, Moodle.
- Also for better Productivity we use Aigle SCRUM methodologies.

Address Sanavi, Cube Incubation, Teknopark Bulvarı, Pendik/İstanbul, 34930, İstanbul, Türkiye

09/08/2023 - CURRENT İstanbul, Türkiye

Developer of software ARKHE

- <u>Image Processing</u> operations with python and opency for Unnamed Aerial Vehicle maden by Gedik University Students (<u>Gedik University Technology Team</u>)in past

01/11/2023 - 28/12/2023 İstanbul, Türkiye

Softwre Support Intern Mobitek Marketing Group

- Dealing SQL Quieries of campaign of clients company.
- Import, Export Excel datas to e-commerce site using admin panel.

12/06/2023 - 14/07/2023 İstanbul, Türkiye

Programmer Istanbul Gedik University Software Office

-Making E-Commerce Site with PHP Laravel for Learning purpose as INTERN.

18/07/2022 - 25/09/2022 İstanbul, Türkiye

Software developer TOMYA Teknoloji A.Ş

- Making Back End Operations in ASP .NET Core 3.1, 6.0 Web API, SQL Server, Mongo DB for learning purpose as INTERN.

Address Maslak Mah. Büyükdere Cad. Spine Tower No: 243/10, 34485 Sarıyer/İstanbul, 34485, İstanbul, Türkiye

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

12/10/2021 - CURRENT İstanbul, Türkiye

Computer Engineer Istanbul Gedik University

Address Cumhuriyet, İlkbahar Sk. No:1, 34876 Kartal/İstanbul, 34876, İstanbul, Türkiye Website https://www.gedik.edu.tr

LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Turkish

Other language(s):

English

Listening B2 Spoken production B1 Reading B2 Spoken interaction B2

German

Listening A2 Spoken production A2 Reading A2 Spoken interaction A2

Writing A2

Writing B2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user